pngfacts.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy - PNG Facts

## Privacy Policy  \- PNGFACTS.COM

Privacy Policies We understand the privacy of visitors to PNGFACTS.COM and is important to us. 

At PNGFACTS.COM , we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit the site, and how we safeguard your information.

We do not sell any kind of personal information to third parties or use this data for any illegal activities.

 **Log Files**  
We may collect Log files  when you visit the site. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Chorme, Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visit.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit this site.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

 **Google AdSense**  
The Google's AdSense program uses the DoubleClick DART cookie. Google's use of the DART cookie enables this site to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We do not control the type of ads google will serve to you when you visit this site. 

 **Email Addresses**  
We do not sell your email addresses that you use to contact us or subscribe to any of our information services via email.
